Yum!
Tonkatsu curry is so good!
Hey, Blade. You've got food on your face.
I'll wipe it clean.
Ah!
What are you two doing?!
You brought it up.
Heya.
Anna, mind if we join you?
You're still calling me Anna?
Not that I mind.
Thanks, Anna.
Hey, Blade.
How do these outfits look on us?
How, you ask?
Oh, I suddenly feel so self-conscious.
That's right. Today's the day, isn't it?
Congratulations on moving up,
all four of you.
Huh?
You mean they're all in the advanced class?
Didn't even notice, huh?
That's why we're allowed to dress freely now.
So how do we look?
Any thoughts?
I bet you're freezing.
Why, how do you do, my fair ladies?
Oh! I'm utterly entranced by your beauty!
Um...
Hey, Anna.
Who's this gorgeous fella here?
I'm quite flattered, really.
Unfortunately, I love all
women in equal measure.
I cannot let myself be bound to just one.
We get it, Leonard.
Anyway, Blade, have you heard?
Hmm?
I hear His Majesty the King is having a
magical beast brought here to the school.
You mean we have to fight it for training?
No way, that's way too extreme...
Hmm...
"Hmm," you say?!
It's a magical beast!
Well, I wouldn't put it past that old fart.
"Old fart"?! That's lèse-majesté!
Whatever, he deserves it.
An earthquake?!
Blade.
Wait, could it be...
Everyone!
We should have everyone take shelter.
Sheesh.
Episode 3
Cu Chulainn
Someone call for His Majesty!
He's the only one who can handle a dragon!
Be careful!
Take cover!
This is the magical beast?
What?
A dragon?!
Wait!
Look out!
You there, get back!
Run for it!
Sit!
There.
Blade, did you just subdue a
dragon with your bare hands?
Huh? This one's still young.
You must have been scared,
being dragged all the way here.
Or are you hungry?
Here.
Too spicy for you?
No way... Without any weapons?
A dragon, with one blow?
I can't believe it!
No way, this is normal!
It's normal, right?
It's not like it's a Great Dragon,
or an Ancient Dragon!
Anyone could take down this
little dragon with a single hit!
Um, well...
Eh?!
Huh?
B-Behind you!
Behind me?
Parent!
Whoa, what?!
So you're my parent!
Parent?
Wait, what are you going on about?
I've finally found you, Parent!
So play with me!
I'll go and find your parents later.
There.
Anyway, where did that dragon run off to?
Th-Th-The dragon shrank
down into that little girl!
Play with me!
Parent, play with me!
Huh? That's impossible!
Play with me!
Hey, be quiet for a second!
Aye.
If you insist, I am more
than willing to be quiet.
Mm-hmm.
So, where's the dragon?
Like I said, that girl...
Surely you joke.
Blade. I saw it, too.
Her true form is a dragon.
What?!
She's a dragon, for real?
That's what I've been saying!
Why do you believe Sophie and not me?!
Parent.
I did as you said and stayed quiet.
A whole ten seconds, just for you.
Now play with me!
Wait, why are you calling me your parent?!
That punch earlier was something else!
I'd expect nothing less from my parent!
Parent!
Play with me! Play with me!
Wh-What now?
Play with me!
Play with me! Play with me! Play with me!
The roots of my horns are sensitive!
Don't be rough with them!
Sure, got it.
How'd I end up doing this?
That tickles!
Hey, don't run away, Cu!
Parent!
What does the name you gave me,
Cu Chulainn, mean?
It's the name of a devoted knight, who was
really strong and always kept promises.
Aye. I can keep a promise.
A dragon upholds an oath
even if it costs them their life.
Blade?
Where are you, Blade?
Y-You moron!
If you were in the bath,
you should have said so!
Hey, you didn't give me any time to respond!
So, did you learn anything?
Oh, yeah.
Magical beasts, including dragons,
are creatures who seek out strength.
When one is vanquished, its flesh may perish,
but a fragment of its soul lingers
as an agglomerate of knowledge.
And when that soul becomes
incarnated as another entity,
it mimics the shape of the
stronger being that finished it off.
Perhaps it's an evolutionary
instinct to seek out strength.
So you mean a dragon defeated by a
human can end up taking a human form?
But it's an extremely rare occurrence.
Not a lot of humans can take down
a high-level beast like a dragon.
Huh? Y-Yeah, you're right!
You think Cu was vanquished
by a human in her past life?
Cu? That's her name?
Did you give her that name, Blade?
That's right!
It's a name that pleases me greatly!
What?!
What's wrong, Earnest?
You pervert!
Unbelievable!
What was that for?
Parent, I'm hungry!
You can feed yourself, you know.
Here.
I'm perfectly capable of
feeding myself, of course.
However, being fed by Parent makes
the food taste that much better!
Um, do you mind if I also feed Cu?
No!
I won't be friends with weakling humans!
There, there.
Hey! Look at how scared Claire is.
You're my parent now,
so you should only pay attention to me!
In the morning, you need to
give me good morning smooches,
and for meals, you must let me
sit in your lap and feed me!
Ah. Yeah, yeah.
You do that?!
Do what?
Morning... smooches...
I haven't done that.
Besides, you spend all your time
staring at mature adult female bodies!
I find that unacceptable!
What?!
Hey, don't go wandering off by—
Wait, Blade!
You were staring?
At what, exactly?
Sounds like he's guilty.
What an awful thing to do!
He's guilty, all right...
Guilty!
Not gentlemanly at all.
I can only describe you as despicable.
Well, then...
By unanimous verdict,
we the jury find Blade guilty.
Um, Earnest...
Blade's looking at us
like he wants to join in.
And so what if he does?
Oh, no...
Never mind.
Hey! Cu!
Wanna join me?
I don't need any training,
but if you insist, Parent,
I'm more than willing to show off my power.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Blade.
We were told to group up with you.
Show us the ropes for the advanced class.
Oh, sure thing.
Hey, I was hoping to specialize
in espionage as a spy.
Who should I have teach me?
Sophie would be the one with those skills.
Sophity!
...Ty?
What?
Then I guess it'll be us four.
Oh, almost forgot.
Huh?
Where did Cu run off to?
Cu?
Man, she never listens to me.
Nothing beats morning smooches!
That girl's back again.
If you're interested, wanna join in?
We'd be happy to have you.
Won't you be friends with us?
You're no match for me at all.
What were you up to, Cu?
Nothing.
Never mind that, Parent.
My stomach is empty!
I'm starving!
Okay, tonkatsu curry it is!
You know me too well!
But don't make it spicy!
Also, I absolutely refuse to eat carrots!
Blade, are you in there?
Dragons are tormented by their parents
immediately after they're born.
The child, learning that something
stronger than it exists,
imprints onto that thing as its parent.
So that's why?
Maybe she's been alone since she was born.
You realize though, don't you?
You can't keep pretending to be her parent.
I know that.
But if I'm not there as her parent,
she'll end up truly alone in the world.
You know how much it
hurts to be alone, right?
That's not fair!
How am I supposed to argue
anything after that?
Sorry.
It's fine.
Now I know that you were serious when
you decided to take care of her.
That reassured you as well, right, Sophie?
Sophie?!
Wait, you didn't realize she was there?
I ran into her on my way to your room.
She's just like me.
Looks like she was worried about you.
Things are going well with Cu,
and there's nothing to worry about.
I see.
I'll be heading back, too.
I wouldn't want rumors to spread about
me sneaking off at night to see a boy.
Huh?
What's wrong, Cu?
Looking at those calms me down.
The moons, huh?
The big one's the parent,
and the small one's the child.
That's why they're always together.
I would look up at them all the time
when I was alone in the wasteland.
Hey, Cu...
Deep down, don't you want to make friends?
Parent, you're gravely mistaken.
Dragons are far sturdier than humans,
both physically and mentally.
We do not form flocks.
We live alone, and we die alone.
That's what it means to be a dragon.
Therefore, I have no need for friends at all!
Besides, the only one I need is you!
You sure are strong, Cu.
That hurts, Parent!
I swear, you sure are hopeless.
Do you realize exactly who I am?
This isn't a day care center.
Look, who else can I turn to?
We're the only two people
who can look after Cu.
So, where's Cu?
Oh, do I have a story for you.
You're so adorable!
Cuddle, cuddle.
Ow, that smarts!
Your beard is so prickly!
Is that an attack?
Are you attacking me?!
She burst out of the room, just like that.
You can't even babysit?!
So useless!
Oh!
Being reprimanded isn't half-bad!
Scold me harder!
This guy's a goner.
Sheesh...
Where in the world did Cu go?
Come now!
You mustn't bully that dragon whelp!
Why, the poor thing!
Agh! You've got the wrong idea, Blade!
I wasn't bullying her!
Glower!
You fool! That won't work!
What?! My eyebeam attack!
Are those dolls supposed
to be me and Earnest?
Bullying is wrong! Always!
Earnest, you're incorrigible!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
You fool! I won't accept your apology!
What awful slander.
Oh!
Can you please be friends with my daughter?
Roger. Totes can do.
Sophie?
Head pats for Cu!
Not fair, Claire!
I want to pat her head, too!
Claire and Yessica, huh?
Oh! I love all women in equal measure.
That's gotta be Leonard.
That said, she sure is observant.
Hello, Altia.
Good morning, Ilya.
Makino, late again?
Karima, good day to you.
Marcia, Michael, Eddy.
How have you all been?
Curtis, Isabella, Marie, Alan.
See you tomorrow.
James, Sarah, Zuimos, Herrera, Olga, Irina!
I haven't heard these names before...
Every student in the school?
No way...
Oh!
That makes 108 friends for my daughter!
I didn't even notice...
Oh, did you find Cu?
Wh-What?!
You idiot! Stop that!
Hey! Cut it out, Blade!
Tell me exactly what happened.
What Cu needs are friends.
Yes, I agree.
But it's not possible because of her nature.
Dragons can't acknowledge anyone
weaker than them as an equal.
It's not in their nature.
For her to recognize someone as her friend,
they need to defeat her.
It doesn't mean anything if I beat her.
I can't be her friend.
There's nothing I can do...
Nope. There's nothing you can do.
In that case, turn to someone else!
You can't fix it all by yourself!
If so, then depend on others.
I asked you for help not too long ago.
It's unfair!
I relied on you,
yet you won't do the same!
What intolerable arrogance!
Well, um...
Just shut up and reach out for help!
From me!
From all of us!
Wait, is that...
The Empress?!
The new kid's with her, too.
I have a favor to ask all of you.
You know Cu, don't you?
I want you to fight Cu,
a dragon, and beat her!
Easier said than done...
We can't go up against a dragon.
I'm begging you!
Please become friends with my daughter!
I'm asking you as well.
Please, fight alongside me.
Empress?!
Oh no, Lady Earnest!
We're here to make the same request.
Why?
We're worried about Cu as well.
Please, everyone.
Do it for us.
Please!
We're on our knees here!
O-Okay, we'll do it!
Please stop kneeling!
We'll do whatever you want!
That's more like it!
This is the kind of hands-on
training I wanted to see!
But you know, Gil,
will a dragon even acknowledge defeat
if it's taken down by such a large group?
Why, sure.
In the eyes of a dragon, humans are
creatures that work collectively.
Do you consider bees cowardly
for fighting as a swarm?
No.
To a dragon, humans are the same.
They wouldn't consider it playing dirty.
That said, it's a shame I won't
be able to watch him fight.
I won't mind if you accidentally
breathe fire on that old blowhard.
Hey, Cu.
I hear that when the humans captured you,
they sprung a trap on you, so you
couldn't fight to your heart's content.
It must have been frustrating.
This time, it'll be fair and square.
Go on and see just how
tough we humans can be.
Show everyone what your strengths are!
Everyone!
Here we go!
Yes, ma'am!
Next Time
The Rosewood Academy Training Exercise